# Yichi (Lyric) Liu

lyricliu@gatech.edu

+1 (770) 769 - 7254



# 2

### Personal Statement

I specialize in web design & development, illustration, video & animation.

My design approach roots in strategic thinking that extends to visual designs crafted with intent. I strive to make all my projects beautiful and elegant. Armed with the latest technologies I have a head full of ideas.

# **★** My Specialties

01. Computer		02. Knowledge
Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustratior	• • • • • • • • •	Grid & Layout
CorelDRAW		Typograph
HTML / CSS JavaScript / Jquery	• • • • • • • • •	Color theory  Animation theory
D3.js / node.js	• • • • • • • •	Prototyping
Adobe After Effects Adobe Premiere	• • • • • • • • •	Image editing Web usability
Cinema 4D Autodesk Maya	• • • • • • • • •	Interface Design
Unity 3D	• • • • • • • • •	



#### Experience

Oct. 2015 - July. 2016

#### Cowoof Application Development

Participated in a social networking application development as a freelancer. Cowoof is a California company for dog lovers.

Jun. 2015 - Aug. 2015

HiMedia Company (Shenzhen) UI design Internship Designed web UI for side projects. Planned an online marketing activity which engaged more than ten thousands participants.

Oct. 2012 - July. 2014

#### Non-profit Organization Enactus Involvement

Participated in a female assistant project supported by Walmart. Received Elite Student 2013 Award from Enactus - China.

#### Education

Aug. 2016 - May. 2018

Georgia Institute of Technology

MS. in **Digital Media** 

Sep. 2012 - Jun. 2016

Huazhong University of Sci. & Tech.

BA. in Communication BE. in Computer Science

Major **GPA: 3.91 / 4.0**, Rank: **No.1** / 30

Jan. 2015 - May. 2015

University of California Berkeley

Visiting Student in Sociology

## Recognitions

10%

Jun. 2016

Outstanding Graduate
Huazhong U. of Sci. & Tech.

%

Sep. 2014

National Scholarship Ministry of Education of China

st

Nov. 2014

**Grand Prize Winner**Wuhan HTML5 Game Design Contest

# Language Skills

Chinese Mother Language English
Advanced Level

**German**Basic Level



#### My hobbies









